<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="song_content">
        <item>Sunrise\n\nInstrumental</item>
        <item>The Climber\n\nHe was a man, a man drowned by the crowd
\nHe was a piece, in a giant chessboard
\nHe was a dot, from the others so close
\nBut was thirsty, and knew where water was
\n
\nWhen he first came to the Great Wall of Love
\nThe doors were closed, he stayed long outside
\nFrom higher they were spitting on his pride
\nBut he didnt turn back and let them laugh
\n
\nHe waited for the night, and jumped over the wall
\nHe ran in the city, seeking a place to hide
\nThe guardians had seen him, they came close to his side
\nBut the shadows he reached heard fade away their calls
\n
\nAnd he waited again, it wasnt his time yet
\nHe was still thirsty then, but stayed in the shadows
\nFor some time he could be patient, hide and speak low
\nBut he was nurturing the freedom’s hope he kept
\n
\nAnd while he was waiting, lying down on the street
\nNobody rescued him, no one brought him water
\nThe people passing by were staring at their feet
\nBut the time will come soon to raise his own banner
\n
\nHe was a man, a man drowned by the crowd
\nHe was a piece, in a giant chessboard
\nHe was a dot, from the others so close
\nBut was thirsty, and knew where water was
\n
\nAnd winter slowly  passed as he grew much stronger
\nThe pain had reinforced his determination
\nThe whole city had changed, hate was out of fashion
\nPeople were divided, so he could speak louder
\n
\nHe learnt how to be, to pretend, and to think
\nThen openly stood up against hypocrisy
\nPointing the outside, the crowd about to sink
\nHe proved they were a full part of humanity
\n
\nHe was a man,a man drowned by the crowd
\nHe was a piece, in a giant chessboard
\nHe was a dot, from the others so close
\nBut was thirsty, and knew where water was
\n
\nFeeling the storm coming, the Great of the city
\nWho feigned to discover the silent misery
\nReasonably agreed to open all the doors
\nHumbly apologized and brought him to the throne
\n
\nBut the thirst was all quenched and he had the power
\nSo smiling to the crowd, smiling to his pieces
\nHe closed the door\n</item>
        <item>Revenger\n\nI roam in suffering, carrying internally
\nThe scars of a king fed with cupidity
\nLiving to reach my aim, to win a gory game
\nFaithful to my anger, I am the revenger
\n
\nAlone through the night, I am recalling my memories
\nMy clan was so bright, stolen legacies
\nMy foes feed my hate, murdering more than I could tell
\nI follow my fate, to lead them straight to hell
\n
\nI will slay their lives, red rills will meander, they will drown
\nIn oceans of cries, an agony tide
\nMy sanity dies, I feel the fury storming inside
\nBleeding from my eyes, my burdened tears fall down
\n
\nMy grief consumes my heart, I am so close to burn
\nOn my path there is darkness from which I cannot return
\nAfter years of training, I walk towards my enemy
\nA royal army to defeat, to honor my family!
\n
\nFor vengeance I fight, I am the revenger
\nDeadly be my might, I will make them suffer
\nCome has the day for them to face their doom!
\nThey will crawl so close to lose their souls
\nThey can’t tame the beast inside of me
\nTonight they are paying for their sins
\nSuffering and hate now I deliver
\nFor vengeance I fight, I am the revenger
\n
\nAfter a timeless fight, after a bloody night
\nI am not sure of my doom, not sure to heal my wounds
\nBut my sorrow comes back, blinding my faith once again
\nI fill with rage
\nStrike back!
\nAnd my force grows in my veins
\nBinding my foes to their decay
\nThe will of justice is here to be spread
\nSo fierce is my wrath
\nThey are going to die
\nThe road towards vengeance leads me as a guide
\nMy strength is overdosed
\nUndergone by my foes
\nShould I kill them quickly or let them crawl?
\n
\nTo kill them is my final purpose
\nAnd their graves are shouting them to fall
\nRegrets are weighing them all down
\nTorn apart, my mercy they call
\nFor vengeance I fight, I am the revenger
\nDeadly is my might, here I am the master
\nCome has the day for them to face their doom!
\nThey are crawling so close to lose their souls
\nThey can’t tame the beast inside of me
\nTonight they are paying for their sins
\nSuffering and hate now I deliver
\nFor vengeance I fight, I am the revenger
\n
\nFor vengeance I fight, I am the revenger (X4)\n</item>
        <item>Stolen Crown\n\nAfter my bloody fight through the night to strike back
\nI prowled around insanity (insanity)
\nThis is the price of my revenge
\nI keep roaming through my grief
\n
\nI had a painful battle deep inside my heart
\nOpposing my cold memories to my reason
\nI felt alone and step by step torn apart
\nWithout a doubt, plagued by my demons
\n
\nI keep going to meet infernal madness
\nMy mind is cleft, crushed in the darkness
\nOf my intentions strongly strengthened by my raves
\nI still have a name to carve on a grave
\n
\nI let myself enslaved by my hate
\nTo slay the greedy king that has been merciless
\nBy murdering my kin, my vengeance still awaits
\n
\nAnd darkening lands to find you, the maker of my grief!
\nYour loyal army I have defeated
\nAnd I am from the deadliest depths of the suffering
\nMy rageful roar goes to drag you to nil
\n
\nUndergo my bloodlust! Just turn back to dust!
\nYour doom is mine, your end is getting nigh
\n
\nThe time has come for you to be downed from your throne
\nTo free from your greed this grieved kingdom you own
\nMy raw bestiality that you have triggered yore
\nHas grown beyond your force, you cannot stop me anymore
\n
\nMeet your fate!
\nSealed be your doom!
\nUndergo my rage!
\nLeave your soul!
\nFear my strength!
\nGo to death!
\nYou belong to
\nThe insane revenger!
\n
\nSo demonic is this endless bloody fight!
\nHere we stand both barely still alive!
\nBut I am not gone yet so undergo the wrath
\nOf the man your henchmen have let alive
\n
\nI battered to see you agonize
\nFeel the pain that I will oversize
\nYou know the throne is not made for a man
\nThe human’s mind is not prepared for this task
\n
\nFear me!
\nFear the way
\nThat is leading you
\nStraight to your grave!
\n
\nThe time has come for you to be downed from your throne
\nTo free from your greed this grieved kingdom you own
\nMy raw bestiality that you have triggered yore
\nHas grown beyond your force, you cannot stop me anymore
\n
\nStolen crown, gory agony
\nBroken down, blame the destiny
\nDeadly game of the revenger
\nTonight your hopes have all been murdered
\nHave all been murdered
\n</item>
        <item>Escape the Sunshine\n\nHidden in the gloom...
\nThey are going to find me
\nIt will be my doom
\nWhich I want to flee
\n
\nAlways in the shade
\nBrightness tends to hurt me
\nIf I let them light me
\nAll my hopes will fly away
\nFly away...
\n
\nBeyond
\nMy sight
\nAway
\nSomething...
\nBut I couldnt tell what
\n
\nStrange sound
\nIn the night
\nAre they
\nComing..?
\n
\nI want to escape the sunshine
\nMy eyes are burning all along
\nI want to escape the moonlight
\nInto the darkness I belong
\nInto the darkness, whoa...
\n
\nThey promised us joy
\nAnd love, and liberty
\nIt’s just a decoy
\nThey have no pity
\n
\nLights and shapes are wrong
\nCome with us, they say
\nYou have to stay strong
\nOr all your hopes will fly away
\nFly away…
\n
\nSlaves of
\nEvil
\nAway
\nSomething…
\nBut I couldnt tell what
\n
\nFull of
\nHatred
\nAre they
\nComing..?
\n
\nI want to escape the sunshine
\nMy eyes are burning all along
\nI want to escape the moonlight
\nInto the darkness I belong
\nInto the darkness, whoa...
\n
\nLike a lightning tearing the skies
\nOr a solar eclipse...
\nIf light and darkness can collide,
\nI wont survive the clash…
\n
\nI want to escape the sunshine
\nMy eyes are burning all along
\nI want to escape the moonlight
\nInto the darkness I belong
\n
\nCause they will hunt me all my life long
\n</item>
        <item>Fears of a Mad Realist?\n\nWhat a beautiful day I had in my country
\nThe sun sweetly hidden by the plane trees shadow
\nOn the stream a big ship has sailed, white as snow
\nAnd I dont know why but it made me feel happy
\n
\nToday Ive a fever, Im feeling ill or sad
\nBut what could justify that once I was so glad?
\nWhat’s turned my happiness into melancholy?
\nFeels like the airs full of powers of mystery
\n
\nTonight I locked myself in my room
\nIm scared... Of what?
\nIm listening... To what?
\nThen I lie and wait for my snaky sleep to come...
\n
\nIn this deep sleep I feel someone else in the room
\nIn a shiver of anxiety I look around
\nJust in front of my bed he is inspecting me
\nI stay there like a corpse, I feel him - I cant see
\n
\nAnd then hes strangling me!
\nI want to move - I cant
\nI want to scream - I cant!
\nAnd I want to get free from this suffocation!
\n
\nSuddenly I wake up, frightened and all sweaty
\nQuickly I light the room and look all around me
\nSeeking my murderer as if he had been blown
\nBut you’re disturbed, you only find that youre alone!
\n
\nOh! Poor humans we are! We cant see anything
\nCant see our tormentors, so limited feelings!
\nThe clock striking away, I stay, waiting for him
\nTheres someone in my head, possessing me, it seems
\n
\nPerhaps Im mad, oh how I wish! But my reason
\nHas not left me. If it were only a vision!
\n
\nFinally he exists. I’ve seen! I cannot doubt
\nAnymore. A dreadful being in my thoughts
\nPicking my slightest dreams, making them disappear
\nI cant see him, I cant touch him, he is my fear!
\n
\nOh! Poor humans we are! We cant see anything
\nCant see our tormentors, so limited feelings!
\nThe clock striking away, I stay, waiting for him
\nTheres someone in my head, possessing me, it seems
\n
\nFluid like a cold wind, he invaded my mind
\nAnd made it its own place, leaving my soul helpless
\nWhen he comes hes stronger, in front of him were blind
\nYou cant escape from him, hell become your madness
\n
\nSo weak, you can hardly hear me, but I am here
\nYou cant see me, you cant touch me, I am your fear!
\n
\nOh! Poor humans we are! We cant see anything
\nCant see our tormentors, so limited feelings!
\nThe clock striking away, I stay waiting for him
\nTheres someone in my head, possessing me, it seems
\n
\nNo! The slave will rebell! Ill take him unawares!
\nThen lock him in the room and burn it all away!
\n
\nHe must have gone
\nHe must be dead
\nDead? Him? Hes better than a man
\nNo, even the Time he can face
\nNo, I feel him again!
\nSo if hes alive, I must already be dead.
\n</item>
        <item>Fading Away\n\nCircled by hatred, my mind is so deeply stricken!
\nYour world is pitiless, I am as wounded as frightened!
\n
\nI hardly see the distant light to which we all must run!
\nAll around me is black, and afar, it’s already begun!
\nWhy don’t you understand? You have to find the will to change!
\nBefore there’s no return! Before the light completely fades out!
\n
\nBecause the end of our universe comes so fast
\nBefore the last light fades away...
\nI feel the pain...
\n</item>
        <item>The Pain Inside\n\nAnd I feel the pain carrying the fury, the anger and the tears
\nAnd I feel the sorrow screaming and wrecking everything inside me
\n
\nI have walked away as a pariah
\nThe loneliness has gained my desperate heart
\nI saw the cold red winter sky of my light
\nI am waiting for my final sunrise
\nRecalling the past, I am shaking with fright
\nAll the black sights of horrors I have seen
\nConsumed all my mind, forsaken I feel
\nSoon falling down, I am aching and done
\n
\nAnd I feel the pain carrying the fury, the anger and the tears (woah)
\nAnd I feel the sorrow screaming and wrecking everything inside me (woah)
\nAnd I feel the darkness circling, I crawl under the suffering (woah)
\nAnd I feel all my thoughts withering, amidst my nightmares and my dreams (waoh)
\n
\nMy dreams were hopeless, I am fading and weak (weak)
\nMy fears are timeless, death appeals to me
\nTorn by the dread, in my soul nothing’s left
\nI am led to my grave, led to my sunset...
\n
\nAnd I feel the pain carrying the fury, the anger and the tears (rire)
\nAnd I feel the sorrow screaming and wrecking everything inside me
\n
\nAnd I feel the pain carrying the fury, the anger and the tears (woah)
\nAnd I feel the sorrow screaming, and wrecking everything inside me (woah)
\nAnd I feel the darkness circling, I crawl under the suffering (woah)
\nAnd I feel all my thoughts withering amidst my nightmares and my dreams (woah)
\n
\n</item>
        <item>Decayed\n\nHey child, dont you want to play ?
\nHey child, dont you want to live ?
\nCatch the bird before it flies away
\nCatch the sun before it falls again
\n
\nIm leaving, Im leaving now
\nIm grown up, Im falling down
\nSlowing down, tired of running
\nDreams are gone, almost sleeping
\nIm leaving, Im leaving you
\nGoing to a higher world, they say
\nHope, the last refuge, runs away
\nIm forgetting you, but my soul remains
\n
\nSoon, your life will take another shape
\nAnd your world now begins to fade
\nThe bird now flees and flies away
\nThe sun now falls and you follow
\n
\nIm leaving, Im leaving now
\nIm grown up, Im falling down
\nSlowing down, tired of running
\nDreams are gone, almost sleeping
\nIm leaving, Im leaving you
\nGoing to a higher world, they say
\nHope, the last refuge, runs away
\nIm forgetting you, but my soul...
\n
\nHey child, where are you going ?
\nHey child, are you leaving them ?
\nThe bird has flown away
\nYou have fallen
\n</item>
        <item>Lightened Hell\n\nRuined by eternal fights, fire and flames lighten the night
\nShed amidst the burning chaos coloured with old blood
\nBattlefield of thousands of wars, lands are consumed by our wrath
\nAll our tombs dug by the bombs as inferno gets around
\n
\nIn this world we all suffer
\nThe pain has taken over
\nThese lands are fed with anger
\nAs hatred is our master
\n
\nWhen come back the death bringers, this burdened hell gets lighter
\nThe souls of soldiers are liberated forever
\nToo many bullets fly and lighten the ablaze sky
\nBattlefield of thousands of dead, drain this stead, slaughter and shred!
\n
\nSince the beginning of time
\nTo batter we need
\nDoes it prove us humans?
\nIs it our identity?
\nCarrying the devil
\nInside everyone
\nIs it a pleasure to fight?
\nAs frenzied animals?
\nSo horrible we are
\nWhy are we divided?
\nDo we love the warfare?
\nAre we all stone-hearted?
\nPassed years were so bloody
\nStill red are the fields
\nWhat is wrong with this realm?
\nWith this humanity?
\n
\nFar in this hell
\nThe stealth bombers drop their hate
\nDie in the flames
\nOr live in an eternal rampage
\n
\nAre we our own masters?
\nOr serving our anger?
\nAll slaves of the fever
\nStill feeding our hunger
\nPlaying with people’s guts
\nTo get the goal of our quest (What quest?)
\nIs there another way
\nThan the one going to darkness?
\n
\nCrime forever
\nThe scythe will soon reap the whole world
\nBurn lose your mind
\nAnd get totally broken down
\n
\nTonight the world dies
\n</item>
        <item>On the Styx\n\nSail on the Styx
\nLet yourself swing and sway
\nThrough the darkened mist
\nYou cant run away
\nDont try to resist
\nBut follow the...
\n
\n...Styx from the spring
\nTo the waterfall
\nIn the depths of hell
\nYour world drowns with you
\nDont try to get through
\nThe strength of the...
\n
\nStyx (the last river) awakes (it will unleash its rage)
\nThe waves (water fury) hit your ship (it will flood your lives)
\nThe storm (rain and thunder) rumbles till your deaths
\n
\nBlood and tears
\nOf the lost fallen
\nFlow through the river
\nPath of oblivion
\nPoisonous as fear
\nOverwhelming…
\n
\nStyx (the last river) awakes (it will unleash its rage)
\nThe waves (water fury) hit your ship (it will flood your lives)
\nThe storm (rain and thunder) rumbles till your deaths
\n</item>
        <item>The Last World\n\nThe Earth is falling apart, it is too late to save it
\nConsumed part by part, sinking slowly
\nIn a last madness that no one can treat
\nStarting to burn with hate, a path we cant escape
\n
\nWhen the world became useless, we decided to leave it dead
\nAfter long years of destruction, a total extermination
\nWe went to space to find new worlds, dragging them towards their loss
\nConquering other lands, making more annihilation
\n
\nWe continue to find more grounds to delay our countdown,
\nAnd slaughter all population with nuclear deflagrations
\nEnslave them with cosmic despair, ignite them and end their fate
\nLight the space with lasers, let them collapse on the planets
\n
\nWith blasting ionic cannons, drag them towards their graves
\nMighty fighters of the Earth conquer the limitless space
\nTake a look around to see this apocalyptic nightmare
\nUnleash your rage upon the orbital fortress we must take!
\n
\nWe have powered cataclysms in all parts of the galaxy,
\nEveryone has forgotten how were peaceful territories
\nDying people are howling, regretting their destiny
\nTrying to stay alive, screaming through the
\nnight
\n
\nAll worlds are dead now making the only path to the final realm
\nOur passed ways are still aching, the ultimate war begins,
\nWe all are so close to the shore, the last world will cry forevermore
\n
\nTo all the peoples, you belong to us!
\nSing your last orisons, you have no defense
\nFury comes from above, pry the stricken skies!
\nThe spree carries on! Dance until you die!
\n
\nThere is no more place to conquer in the universe
\nSo keep on fighting until wreck their final resistance
\nThe brave soldiers of the human race are still fearless
\nFreeing the terror that will spread dread on this age
\n
\nWarriors of deathly armies, fly towards the fight!
\nDeliver pain and fury from apocalyptic times!
\nWith plasma storms, annihilate all the battle wastelands!
\nWarmachines slaughter all foes in opponents ranks!
\nDark skies are disrupted by the clashing armies
\nThe night has died into the light of this perfect misery
\n
\n(Using always more explosions to overthrow the enemies)
\n
\nAll worlds are dead now making, the only path to the final realm
\nOur passed ways are still aching, the ultimate war is raging,
\nThe sundown is coloured with blood, ablaze is the horizon
\nWe all are so close to the shore, the last world cries evermore
\n
\nWe have sought and destroyed the entire infinity
\nNow exterminated is what we all will be...
\n
\nAll is lost and already done, everything just fades
\nFlying over a dead world, erasing emotions on our faces
\nThis realms withers to nil, there is no way to live
\nLooking through the bloody mist, recognising the hell
\n
\nAll worlds are dead now making, the only path to apocalypse
\nOur passed ways are still aching, the ultimate war is ending
\nThe sundown is coloured with blood, ablaze is the horizon
\nWe all are far beyond the shore, the last world cannot cry anymore!
\n
\nWe have destroyed the last world
\nAnd brought apocalypse in every world
\nOur end has come so fast
\nNow I wait for the final blast
\n</item>
        <item>Sunset\n\nAnd Im finally standing here
\nWhen all has gone, life and fear
\nNear is the destruction
\nOf my dying sun
\n
\nColouring in red the cold sea
\nLighting the ruins of the city
\nHot was the sun, hot is the dust
\nFrom the last vestige of our past
\n
\nA storm has passed, a final sigh
\nAnd I can only remember
\nAll these flames, falling from the sky
\nAnd all the tears and my anger
\nAll these flames, falling from the sky
\nAnd all the fear that I suffered
\n
\nOur world is down
\nOur world is drowned
\nAll my lifes gone
\nAnd hopes been wind-blown
\n
\nA storm has passed, a final sigh
\nAnd I can only remember
\nAll these flames falling from the sky
\nAnd all the tears and my anger
\nAll these flames, falling from the sky
\nAnd all the fear that I suffered
\n
\nIve seen too much, Ive fought too long
\nAnd Ill just walk right to the red sea
\nTo sink in its tranquility
\nLife is over but love still strong
\n
\nNow I long for the extinction
\nof my dying sun.
\n</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>